The story of four souls who needed a body and one guy who needed some soul.
Heart and Souls is a fantasy, comedy, romance film directed by Ron Underwood.
A fateful night in 1959, four people die when the bus they are riding crashes.
They continue as ghosts; their souls become eternally entwined to the life of
a child born at the moment of their deaths as his guardians.
Baby Thomas grows up to be a businessman who has memories of his playmates,
but assumes they are products of his youthful imagination.
When the ghosts realize they need Thomas' help to move on to the
afterlife, they decide to make an appearance once more.
Thomas Reilly, played by Robert Downey Jr..
Harrison Winslow, played by Charles Grodin.
Penny Washington, played by Alfre Woodard.
Julia, played by Kyra Sedgwick.
Milo Peck, played by Tom Sizemore.
Hal the Bus Driver, played by David Paymer.
Heart and Souls is a 1993 American fantasy
comedy-drama film directed by Ron Underwood.
The film stars Robert Downey Jr.
as Thomas Reilly, a businessman recruited by the souls of four deceased people, his guardian angels from childhood,
to help them rectify their unfinished lives, as he is the only one who can communicate with them.
The film explores themes of businessman, afterlife, san
francisco, california, supernatural, redemption.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.